NKOSINATHI

MTSHALI

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am writing to express my interest in the Full-Stack Developer position at your Company. As a full-stack developer with experience in Java, Ionic, Python, and Angular, I am confident that I have the skills and expertise necessary to excel in this role.

In my current position at TcF lcT, I have been responsible for developing and maintaining web applications using a variety of technologies. I have experience working with both front-end and back-end development, and I am comfortable working with databases, APIs, and other tools necessary for building complex web applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TcF lcT

Software Developer

2020 - PRESENT

- Building dynamic and adaptable web applications
- Performing analysis of product development
- Working with back-end programmers to create REST API
- · Creating user interfaces using the AngularJS framework
- Collaborating with other developers, managers, and UX designers in building software

MLAB 2019 - 2020

Intern then Software Developer

- · Building dynamic and adaptable web applications using Angular
- Developing cross-platform mobile applications with a native-like experience using Ionic
- · Delivering comprehensive front-end software
- · Working with back-end programmers to create REST API
- · Creating user interfaces using the AngularJS framework

Projects

- Tipper Mobile App
- Henkel (Safety equipment system)
- · Hats and Shoulders App
- Pre-school App
- Mthomhowolwazi App
- Print Pics App
- Law App

REFERENCE

Fabian Qopane

Computer Science Lecture
Phone 073 457 5813

Ekurhuleni West College

ence Lecture Senior Developer and Facilitate

Nokwanda Mrajane

Mlab

7 5813 Phone: 072 188 3914

CONTACT

- **** 061-471-9972
- ✓ 9mm.ext.gp@gmail.com
- 2367 Rabie Ridge, Midrand
- <u>www.tcfdev.000webhostap</u>

 p.com/

EDUCATION

2015 - 2017 EKURHULENI WEST COLLEGE

 Computer Sciences and Information Technology

2019 - 2020 MLAB

- Angular & Ionic
- RestFull API's
- No SQL Database

2021 - 2022

UMUZI

- Python
- MySQL

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Public Relations
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Design Skills

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- IsiZulu (Fluent)